#### **CONTACT**



786 - 825 - 2591



Miguel.ang.castillo.rojas@gmail.com



Miguel Angel Castillo Rojas



https://miguelcastillo98.github.io

#### **LANGUAGES**

Native Spanish)

English (B1)

Italian (A1)

#### **ACKNOWLEDGMENTS**

First Place: 2016 Taekwondo Regional

Games

Modality: Combat

Awarded by: ASCUN.

First Institutional Place: ICFES Knowledge Tests 2014.

Awarded by: Instituto nuestra señora del carmen (INSCA).

#### Academic excellence

Awarded by: Instituto nuestra señora del carmen (INSCA).

**Certificate:** Application research for critical reading comprehension for 7th and 8th grade students.

Awarded by: Vice-Rectory for Research, Innovation and Entrepreneurship of the Autonomous University of the West. (2021)

## INTERESTS

- Do exercise.
- Practise martial arts.
- Watch movies and series.
- Listen to music.

# **TOOLS AND PROGRAMS**

- Adobe: Photoshop, Illustrator, Audition, Premiere Pro.
- Autodesk Maya
- figma
- Microsoft office: Word, Powerpoint, Excel.
- google tools.
- Arduino
- visualstudio
- Git and GitHub
- Heroku mysql

# REFERENCES

# PERSONAL REFERENCES

Intinazca Pazan Carrera

**Telephone:** (+57) 318 4012 737 Email: Intinazca.pazan@uao.edu.co

Jorge Eliecer Romero

**Telephone:** (+57) 318 523 0738 Email: Juniorromero0824@gmail.com

# FAMILY REFERENCES

Olga Lucia Rojas Henao Telephone: (+57) 316 575 9091

Email: Olgarohe@hotmail.com

# COMPETENCES

- Teamwork.
- Information search.
- Planification and organization.

# Miguel Castillo

# Multimedia Engineer

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

#### Development of user interfaces:

I use my knowledge of HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create attractive and visually stunning user interfaces. I have a strong focus on aesthetics. usability, and user experience, ensuring that my web applications are intuitive and enjoyable to use.

Design implementation and layout: I can carry out the technical implementation of designs provided by graphic designers or design teams, turning them into functional web interfaces. I work with precision in the layout and positioning of elements using frameworks and tools such as Bootstrap or Flexbox.

#### Adaptability and responsive design:

I have experience in creating websites and applications that adapt to different devices and screen sizes. I implement responsive design to ensure a consistent experience across desktop, tablets, and mobile devices.

#### Collaboration in multidisciplinary teams:

I am used to working in multidisciplinary teams, collaborating closely with designers, back-end developers and other professionals to achieve exceptional results. I have effective communication skills and the ability to understand and translate design and technical requirements into functional code.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2/2020 - 3/2020 Cali, Colombia

- UX Designer in the creation of the website for the company Full Potencia.

Contact: Intinazca Pazan Cell: (+57) 318 4012 737

#### Responsibilities:

- Conduct user research and testing.
- Develop prototypes and task flows based on user needs.
- Collaborate with developers to create the optimal platform for usability.

design link

5/2020 - 8/2020

Cali, Colombia

- Junior programmer for the development of statistical data visualization software for the frequency ring method.

Contact: Intinazca Pazan Cell: (+57) 318 4012 737

#### Responsibilities:

- Conceive the software platform for the visualization of statistical data of the frequency rings method using.
- In charge of programming the collection, organization and visualization of the data obtained with the ChartJs library.

5/2022 - 8/2022 Miami, United States

- Redesign and Implementation of the website for the company Miami **Executive Car Service.** 

**Contact:** Edison Cell: +1 (305) 407-0573

## Responsibilities:

- Carry out benchmarking processes and research to understand the business, define user and customer needs.
- Develop high-fidelity prototypes and task flows, based on user needs.
- Carry out tests with users with the proposed design.
- Implement the design of the web page.

**Link:** https://www.miamiexecutivecarservice.com

#### PROGRAMMING SKILLS **OTHER SKILLS**

HTML Velo API **CSS** Adobe Photoshop Adobe After Effects Javascript Adobe Premiere ReactJS ChartJS Adobe Illustrator C# Figma Visual Basic Bootstrap Wordpress

## **EDUCATION**

# MULTIMEDIA ENGINEERING

## 2022

Universidad Autónoma De Occidente, Colombia, Cali